Finding Aid for the Edwin Wendell Pauley Papers, 1907-2001
UCLA Library, Department of Special Collections
- Personal
  - KNX Radio - Citizen of the Week - D. Bracken (Box 128, Folder 6)
  - BIC News - Berkeley Campus Report (Box 128, Folder 7)
  - BPM (Bobbe)- Gold Bookends? (Box 133, Folder 1)
    1 pair
  - NBC Nightly News Segment on Pauley Petroleum (Box 133, Folder 2)
    Beta Cassette
  - (1956-1958)
    - Reading File (Box 53, Folder 1)
    - Reading File (Box 53, Folder 2)
    - Reading File (Box 53, Folder 3)
    - Reading File (Box 54, Folder 1)
    - Reading File (Box 54, Folder 2)
    - Reading File (Box 54, Folder 3)
  - Coconut Island
    - Correspondence, Maps, Magazines, News Clippings, and photocopy of News Clippings (Box 81, Folder 5)
      Includes Hertz Drive Guide - Maui; vol. 11, no. 2
    - Coconut Island for sale - Brochures (Box 82, Folder 2)
      Correspondence and Booklets; f. 1 of 2; Some with Japanese inserts
    - Coconut Island for sale - Brochures (Box 82, Folder 3)
      Correspondence and Booklets; f. 2 of 2
    - Appraisals - Hawaii Marine Laboratory (Box 83, Folder 1)
    - Appraisal Report by F.B. Carter III (Box 83, Folder 2)
      Photographs, Maps, and Manuscripts; 2 copies
    - Appraisal for Sheridan C. F. Ing by Hastings, Martin, Hallstrom, Chew and Voronaeff, Ltd. (Box 83, Folder 3)
    - Appraisal for Walter E. Bliss, Esquire by Philip W. Won (Box 83, Folder 4)
    - Appraisal for Bill Winn by Frank L. Merritt (Box 83, Folder 5)
    - Appraisal Map (Box 83, Folder 6)
      Maps
    - University of Hawaii State and Legislative Bills (Box 83, Folder 7)
    - State Legislature (Box 83, Folder 8)
    - Title Report (Box 83, Folder 9)
    - Honolulu Advertiser Articles 1937-1985 (Box 83, Folder 10)
      Photocopies of News Clippings
    - Attorney General "Opinion" #62-16 (Box 83, Folder 11)
    - Honolulu Advertiser Article, Oct 1985 (Box 83, Folder 12)
    - Honolulu Advertiser Articles, Dec 1955 (Box 83, Folder 13)
    - Letter to William R. Pagen (Box 83, Folder 14)
    - Miscellaneous - 1953 (Box 84, Folder 1)
      Photographs, Correspondence, and News Clippings; f. 1 of 2
    - Miscellaneous - 1953 (Box 84, Folder 2)
      Photographs, Correspondence, and News Clippings; f. 2 of 2
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 99, Folder 1)
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 99, Folder 2)
    - Coconut Island Club (Box 99, Folder 3)
    - Coconut Island Visitors (Box 99, Folder 4)
    - Coconut Island - Miscellaneous (Box 99, Folder 5)
    - Miscellaneous News Clippings (Box 99, Folder 6)
    - Miscellaneous Photographs of Friends and Family on Coconut Island (Box 113, Folder 1)
      Oversized; Photo Albums
    - Coconut Island Guest Book (Box 113, Folder 2)
    - Information on Coconut Island (Box 121, Folder 1)
      Oversized, Correspondence, Blue Prints, and News Clippings
- Photo Albums
  - Eclipse Day (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Bobbe and Bill Pagen on yachting trip (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Coconut Island and Baja California (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - UCLA - Pauley party with L.A. political figures (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - JFK (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - JFK (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - UCLA Archive - Visit of King Hussein of Jordan to the Pauley home (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Visit of King Hussein of Jordan (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - UCLA - Party at Pauley with L.A. political figures (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - UCLA - Political figures and UC Regents at Pauley party (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Graduation Ceremony in Pauley Pavilion (Box 26, Folder 1)
    Includes newsletter - UCLA from the Chancellor's Desk, vol. 6, no. 3
  - Coconut Island album inscribed "MRS. ANN WALKER AND TERRY" on cover and "FONDEST ALOHA FROM BOBBIE AND ED PAULEY" on verso of cover (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - EWP with family and friends on Coconut Island (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Eureka Gasoline (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Coconut Island (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Coconut Island album inscribed "Happy 25th Wedding Anniversary" (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Coconut Island - from Judge Tom, Martha, Peter, and Tom, Jr. (MacBride) to Abner Hale Pauley and Jerusha Hale Pauley (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Shah of Iran California Visit (The) (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Edwin W. Pauley Marine Laboratory - Coconut Island, Oahu, Hawaii (Box 30, Folder 1)
    Oversized; Includes University of Hawaii itinerary, handouts
  - Coconut Island, Salishan, Avalon Mojo, Coconut Island, Sealife Park, Barge Bobbe Jean, Baby Cat, Scott's graduation from Pomona, Bobbe's B-day, and Christmas Eve (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Shah of Iran (The), California visit - Presented by EWP (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Charter Day ceremonies at UCLA (Box 33, Folder 1)
    Oversized; Includes correspondence from Clark Kerr
  - Pagen family pictures (Box 34, Folder 1)
    Oversized; Album disbound
  - EWP and family (Box 35, Folder 1)
    Oversized; Wm. Banks Photography
  - Bobbe and Bill Pagen's trip to Kahala and pets (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Coconut Island (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Visit to Marine Corps Air Station, Kaneohe Bay (Box 37, Folder 1)
    Oversized; Aloha Album
  - Coconut Island and Steve's 40th Birthday Party (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - Coconut Island - Middle Eastern Costume Dinner, swimming with dolphins, water skiing (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Coconut Island (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Coconut Island (Box 39, Folder 1)
    Oversized; Bill Banks Photography
  - Africa - Safari (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Dedication of Pauley Tennis Complex at Pomona (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - PDQ - Petroleum Corporation of Los Angeles (Box 41, Folder 1)
    Oversized; Black bound album with green "Photographs" title on front cover
  - PDQ - Petroleum Corporation of Los Angeles (Box 41, Folder 2)
    Oversized; Black bound album with gold "Photographs" title on front cover
  - Coconut Island Club (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - Bill Brunk Photography (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - Harry S. Truman Commemorative U.S. Postage Stamp (Box 43, Folder 1)
    Oversized; Includes portrait postcard of Harry S. Truman
  - EWP and friends - hunting trip (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - Saga of the Seth Parker - Four-Masted Schooner Owned by Ed and Bobbe Pauley including musical score, Coconut Island by Cherry Zeller (Box 44, Folder 1)
    Oversized; Includes photographs of sailing and Coconut Island, including one negative; Letters with EWP letter head/supplies list
  - Honolulu Chapter of the ARCS Foundation - Luncheon on Coconut Island (Box 44, Folder 2)
    Oversized; Presented to Bobbe and Ed with much love and appreciation from the National Executive Board of the ARCS Foundation
  - College Awards Dinner (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - Bobbe receiving award at California Yacht Club (Box 98, Folder 12)
  - Coconut Island
    - Trip on Yacht Westward (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - EWP and family (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Miscellaneous black and white photographs of family and friends (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Lyndon B. Johnson at Coconut Island (Box 82, Folder 15)
- Photographs
  - JFK (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - EWP with JFK (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - FDR (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - L.B. Johnson's Presidential boat (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Herbert Hoover (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Harry S. Truman (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Mr. and Mrs. Edwin Pauley with the Shah and Empress of Iran (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - EWP with Harry S. Truman (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - EWP with Dwight Eisenhower (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Lyndon B. Johnson and family (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - EWP with Harry S. Truman, Commander Leo and his secretary (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - EWP with Shah of Iran at graduation ceremony (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - UC Regents (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Pauley's 15th wedding anniversary with guest Ethel Merman (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - UC Santa Barbara track (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Los Angeles Worlds Affairs Council (Box 1, Folder 16)
    Includes correspondence from Ray Silvius
  - EWP with Italian Ambassador (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Launching S.S. Mormacdove (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Oslo, Norway (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Loyola Citizenship Day Award - EWP, Rabbi Magnin at the Beverly Hilton (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Extra photos and negatives of the photo album: "Edwin W. Pauley and a few old friends" (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - EWP with plaque from the Edwin P. Pauley Foundation as a Major Donor, with 3 unidentified men (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - EWP with military men (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Los Angeles World Affairs Council - EWP, Senator Birch Bayh, and Rabbi Magnin (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - EWP and Ronald Reagan (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - EWP and family, Harry S. Truman and family (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - EWP with Ed Carter, Harriet and Charles Luckman, and Troy Post (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - EWP with Allison Kaye and the Johnsons (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - EWP with Andy Anderson (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Oil, Gas - Reynosa, Tamaulipas (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - EWP with Prime Minister McMullan of Great Britain, Counsel of Portugal - Joseph Sigal, Counsel General of Great Britain - A.A.E. Franklin (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - EWP with Mayor Sam Yorty (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Louis C. Miriam - Mayor of Detroit (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Bobbe Pauley and Annie Walker (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - EWP, Bobbe Pauley, and Perdie, Admiral Bob and Dorothy Berry (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Richard "Red" Skelton and Georgia (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - EWP and Bobbe, Admiral and Mrs. Ramage - Navy Ball (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Sproul's reception (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - EWP and Korean visitors (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - EWP with Eleanor Roosevelt (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Bobbe Pauley, Ronald Reagan, Nancy Reagan, Billie Greenlaw (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Bobbe Pauley, Governor Albert Rosellini, Ethel Rosellini (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Bobbe Pauley, Ray Olsen, Governor Edmund G. "Pat" Brown, Bernice Layne Brown (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Truman's visit to the Pauleys' home (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - EWP and Edmund G. Brown trip to Mexico City (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Richard Nixon (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Award to EWP from L.A. County Board of Supervisors (Box 2, Folder 25)
    Includes several telegrams and letters
  - L.A. Country Supervisors? Meeting, Award acceptance? (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Pauley Petroleum (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - EWP - World Affairs Council Reception honoring Vice President of Vietnam Nguyen Cao Ky (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Vernon and Mary Cheadle (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Bob Hope and Dolores Hope at the Rose Bowl (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Robert "Red" Skelton and King of Jordan (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - EWP and Franklin Murphy (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - EWP with Dwight E. Eisenhower, Franklin Murphy, and Regents (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Aerial view of the Los Angeles Coliseum (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - EWP with Bobbe Pauley and Lady Bird Johnson (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - EWP with Empress Fara Diba of Iran (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Clark Kerr, JFK, and Franklin Murphy, EWP in background (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - EWP and L.A. Mayor Sam Yorty, Royal Hawaiian Hotel in background (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - EWP with Ann Miller and Bernice Brown (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - EWP with L.A. County Supervisor Warren and Dorn (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Potsdam Conference - EWP and Truman (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - EWP and Bobbe Pauley with Rohan Singh (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - EWP - Regents' Meeting (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - EWP Residence - Beverly Hills (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - EWP with William Beckett and Art Ayres? (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - EWP with Richard "Red" Skelton (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Western Airlines Board of Directors meeting (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - EWP with President Lyndon B. Johnson (Box 3, Folder 20)
    Includes correspondence from Albert G. Pickerell
  - EWP with Dorothy Kirsten Frank (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - EWP with John C. Elliott and wife (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - EWP and Mayor Paulson with (Miss Dewline, polar bear cub) and adult polar bear (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - EWP, Bobbe Pauley, Warren Dorn, Phyllis Dorn, Ernie Debs (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Robert Butler (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - EWP with Vernon Cheadle (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - General Mark Clark at Ceasefire premiere (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Harris and Ewing Photos - Study in moods - EWP at Senate Appropriation Subcommittee (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - EWP with Franklin Murphy, LBJ, and John Frank (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - EWP with JFK, Pat Brown, and Frank Sinatra (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Offices of Pauley Petroleum (Box 3, Folder 31)
    10000 Santa Monica Blvd
  - Lyndon B. Johnson - Statue (Box 3, Folder 32)
    Includes news clippings
  - L.A. World Affairs Council & Town Hall luncheon meeting honoring Secretary of State Dean Rusk (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - EWP and Senator Alan Cranston (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - EWP and Vice President Hubert Humphrey luncheon - Town Hall (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - EWP and Madame Chiang Kai-Shek - World Affairs Council, Beverly Hilton (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - EWP with Admiral Noel Gayler - L.A. World Affairs Luncheon (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - EWP with John Connally - L.A. World Affairs Council Luncheon (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - EWP with Yorty and Echeverria (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - EWP with Barron Hilton, Don Douglas, and Dan Martin - Hilton's Ranch, Northern California (Box 3, Folder 40)
    Includes photocopy and negative
  - EWP with Josip Tito - L.A. World Affairs Luncheon and Yorty Reception (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - EWP with Roy Ash - L.A. World Affairs Luncheon - Secretary of Commerce (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - L.A. World Affairs Council Luncheon honoring Averell Harriman (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - EWP with Congressman Wilbur Mills - L.A. World Affairs Luncheon (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - EWP with Nixon, Reagan - Bohemian Grove (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - EWP and Bobbe Pauley with Supervisor Kenneth Hahn and wife (Box 3, Folder 46)
  - Moose (Box 4, Folder 1)
    Includes postcard of moose and correspondence from Max
  - Red Skelton's performance at Kaneohe Marine Base - Generals Aide (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Delegates: 1st Council of 6th District - Phi Kappa Psi (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Bobbe Pauley - high school (Box 4, Folder 4)
    Includes correspondence from J. Elwin Le Tendre, Principal of Berkeley High School
  - Mission to Japan (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Mary Anne Schenkkau? (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Marie McHenry with Ginny and Bob Josephson on the Lurline (coming home from Coconut Island) (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Marie McHenry and daughter Bobbe Pauley at the Candlelight Ball 1951 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Marie McHenry and daughter Bobbe Pauley (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Marie McHenry with Bob Walker and Atly and Riad Ghali (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Marie McHenry (Dahdear) (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Marie McHenry with Virginia and Edwin (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Ora Condrey, Bobby Rogers, and Bill Rogers at Catalina on Mojo at Solomon's Landing (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Marie Rogers McHenry and daughter Ora Louise McHenry Condrey and Elvirita Bleitz (Mrs. Don) at Bel Air Bay Club - Santa Monica, CA (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Matt's birthday luncheon - Matt, Kevin, Bobs, Tasha, Barry at Bel Air Hotel (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Vicky Pauley - Ellen and Anne (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Puppies - Cappy from Steve and Marylyn to Barbara M. Pagen (Box 4, Folder 17)
    Includes correspondence from Steve and Marylyn
  - EWP and Bobbe Pauley with family at Christmas (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Bobbe Pauley and family (Box 4, Folder 19)
    Includes film negatives and slides
  - Christmas photos (some with Aunt Minnie) (Box 4, Folder 20)
    Includes film negatives
  - Christmas photos (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Family Thanksgiving film negatives (Box 4, Folder 22)
    Includes correspondence from Susie and John and negative from Marylyn
  - BW family photograph (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - The Petrol Corporation (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Eureka Gasoline (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - General Mark Clark (Box 4, Folder 26)
    Includes crossword puzzle with EWP pictured
  - UCLA (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Petrol Refinery - Bandini Blvd. (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Photographs to Bobbe Pauley from Carrol Bennett (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Ode to Coconut Island (and herein lies the completion of Projects B+D) (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Lyndon Johnsons at Coconut Island picnic (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Joanne Condrey Dorward at the Ed and Bobbe Pauleys home on Norton in L.A. - 6-8 yrs. Old (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Ora Louise McHenry, A.H. McHenry, Charles Small, Mrs. Robert McHenry, T.R. Finley, George Maze at Bald Eagle Ranch (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Bobbe and Bill Pagen with Barbara Bush (Box 6, Folder 12)
    Includes correspondence from George F. Moody
  - Harry S. Truman Institute - Replica of Oval Office and copy of news clipping of the Institute's fund-raiser (Box 6, Folder 13)
    Includes correspondence from Donald S. Dawson of the Harry S. Truman Library Institute to Bobbe and background information to the Institute
  - EWP with Bobbe and Harry S. Truman (Box 6, Folder 14)
    Includes correspondence to Ms. Bradley from Bobbe dated - March 21, 1996
  - Miscellaneous film negatives (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Miscellaneous slides (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Annie Walker and Bobbe at Mulewai (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - EWP and Bobbe Pauley at Walker's beach house - Mulewai (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - EWP with Bill Monahau (Cupid) (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - EWP, Bobbe Pauley, and Jane Marshall in Mexico (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Bobbe Marshall in Mexico (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - EWP, Bobbe, and Jane Marshall (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - EWP with Bob Hannegan (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Clyde Leo and Elijie (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Gaye, Aileen?, and Sandra? (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Poncet Davis and ? (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Gaye Bjornsen?, Aileen Pauley?, and Sandra Pauley? (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Bobbe, Susie, and Buzzie (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Clyde Leo and ? (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Bill Hale and Bobbe Pagen (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - EWP, Bobbe Pauley, Bill Hale, Marion Hale, and 2 unidentified people (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - EWP and family and friends at the beach (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - EWP - Retirement from Regents (Box 7, Folder 19)
    Slides
  - Coconut Island (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Tiana - Age 16, Shaylene - 14, Shari and ? (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Coconut Island - Buzz (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Senator and Mrs. Fullbright at Coconut Island (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - EWP and Bobbe Pauley with Gaye, David, and Mary (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Zihuatanejo (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Coconut Island - various gerainiai parties (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - EWP, Bobbe, and friends (Box 7, Folder 27)
    Includes negatives
  - Colonel William Knight USAF (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - William R. Pagen on the U.S.S. John F. Kennedy (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - EWP, Bobbe Pauley, Susan Pauley (age 9), and Marie McHenry (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Fourth of July (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Bobbe Pauley and mother Marie McHenry at Susan's wedding (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - EWP, Bobbe, and grandchildren (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Bobbe with grandchildren (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Bobbe with family and friends (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Michelle Hillyer baby shower (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Bobbe with grandchildren and great grandchildren (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Photographs from Stephen M Pauley to Bobbe Pauley (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Yachts (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - EWP, Bobbe, Red Skelton, Steve, Marie McHenry, Riad, Dinah Shore, George Montgomery, and friends (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - EWP's son and unidentified girl (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Pauley Tennis Complex dedication (Box 10, Folder 23)
    Includes correspondence from Elaina M. Myrinx of Pomona College
  - Black and white photographs of Bobbe, Steve, and family member? (part of military?) (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Bobbe and Michelle Hillyer (Box 10, Folder 25)
    Includes correspondence from Michelle Hillyer
  - Bobbe and family at Tasha's baby shower (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Miscellaneous film negatives of EWP, Bobbe, and friends (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - Hannah Pauley, Bobbe, Scott, Abbie, and Marylyn P. Pauley (Box 10, Folder 28)
    Includes correspondence from Abbie and film negatives of Thanksgiving 1996
  - Film negative of Bobbe and Kevin with leopard (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - Bobbe with dogs and photographs of plants and various shots of the neighborhood (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - Bobbe, Rosemary, Scott, and Abbie in London (Box 10, Folder 31)
  - Scott playing the lute? And girls singing (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Bobbe, Steve, Marylyn, and ? (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Balboa and Palm Springs (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Thanksgiving (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Thanksgiving (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Bobbe at Susie's wedding to Rick-Christie Fox (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Steve Pauley on fishing trip (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - EWP, Bobbe, Newell and Nada Bohnett on Coconut Island (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Thanksgiving (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Steve Marylyn boys - B & B, house, and cat (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Thanksgiving, cat, and dog (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Bobbe and Bill at dinner event (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Hawaii - Kahala (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Waldorf going away, Fort Lauderdale, life boat drill (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Christmas (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Thanksgiving at Steve and Marylyn's (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Film negatives of Scott's graduation from Pomona College (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Clarke Pauley's wedding to Annie and rehearsal dinner (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Bobbe and Christmas tree (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Birthday party - Bobbe Jean and Susie (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Mt. Palomar and Lawrence Hall of Science (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Christmas - Sent to grandchildren on Topaz - Bobbe, Rosemary, Annie, Bill, and Tasha (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Holly, Devan, et al. attending party at 9521 Sunset (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Betty and Bill's 50th anniversary and Harvard graduation (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - William (Bill) Pagen family slides (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - William (Bill) Pagen family slides (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Black and white film negatives - Bob - football; Mom, Patti, Bob, Cindy (William Pagen's family?) (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - William Pagen's family photographs and film negatives (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - EWP with UC Regents (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Trophy presentation to football player (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - EWP at Joseph Scott's birthday (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Elementary school (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - EWP meeting with unidentified man (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Barbara Pauley with Vijaya Lakshmi Pandit (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - EWP and friends at dinner banquet (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Andrew Dowdy, Stafford Warren, John Lawrence, Charles Carpenter, and William Longmire, founders of UCLA School of Medicine presented to EWP (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Film negatives of family at beach and baseball game (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Barbara Pauley (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Alben Barkley (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - EWP and Bobbe with friends on Coconut Island (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - China - EWP with Chiang Kai Shek and Madame Chiang Kai Shek (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Mexico (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Venice Island, Duck Club (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Inauguration of Harry S. Truman (Box 12, Folder 20)
    Includes invitation to Inaugural Dinner and Inaugural Ball
  - EWP and Harry S. Truman at Library Dinner (Box 12, Folder 21)
    Includes correspondence from Robert M. Mount
  - Switzerland (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - EWP and Bobbe at air base - "Dick" Whittington Photography (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - Potsdam Conference (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - Speaker Rayburn 20th Century Fox Tour (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - EWP, Harold and Rancheros (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - EWP at Conquistadores del Cielo 10th Anniversary Fiesta - HF Bar Ranch - Saddlestring, Wyoming (Box 13, Folder 2)
    Includes film negative
  - Dedication of Pauley Memorial Hall - Occidental (Box 13, Folder 3)
    Includes "The President's Report to the Trustees" booklet, newsletter "The Pauley Hall Hellion" and Dedication program
  - Rancheros Ride (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Senator and Mrs. Pepper - Visitor to studio (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Visit to Fort Monmouth (Box 13, Folder 6)
    Includes news clippings and correspondence from Aloysius K. Quinn
  - EWP with Lorman Opie, Chancellor, Washington, President Phi Kappa Psi Alumni Association (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - EWP and Bobbe in Mexico City (Box 13, Folder 8)